export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Floors, aisles, and passageways must be kept clear of wood, tools, material, oil and grease spots, and other objects:",
    options: [
      "Because they may cause someone to slip or trip and fall.",
      "Unless you are in a hurry.",
      "Because they are unsightly.",
      "Because they cause more work for the custodians."
    ],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Loose clothing, jewelry and long hair must be securely fastened or removed:",
    options: [
      "Before operating any machine.",
      "Before the end of class.",
      "Only when you are assisting the instructor.",
      "Only when it will not affect your fashion."
    ],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "All accidents and injuries, no matter how slight, must be:",
    options: [
      "Ignored.",
      "Reported to health services immediately.",
      "Reported to the instructor immediately.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Report and breakage or damage to tools, instruments, or machinery:",
    options: [
      "To no one, you might get in trouble.",
      "To the instructor immediately.",
      "To the instructor after a few minutes or more have passed.",
      "To a TA or a close friend only."
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Horseplay or the distraction of fellow students is never permitted and will result in getting kicked out of this class.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Always look out for fellow students and instructors prior to working.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "You must not talk to, or distract the attention of, a person operating a machine because:",
    options: [
      "Conversation slows down the flow of work.",
      "It is not polite.",
      "The distracted operator or others may be injured.",
      "It is too noisy for conversation in the lab."
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "All special setups, including removal of any safety equipment, must be:",
    options: [
      "Checked by another student.",
      "Approved by the instructor, then returned to normal after the cuts are made.",
      "Need not be approved if you know what you are doing.",
      "Done quickly while no one is watching."
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Throwing objects in the woodshop…",
    options: [
      "Is permitted on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.",
      "No a big deal.",
      "O.k. if it just a small item.",
      "Punishable by being kicked out of class."
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "When unplugging a power tool:",
    options: [
      "Make sure your hands are wet, and you're standing in a puddle.",
      "Pull by the cord itself.",
      "Pull it out by the plug handle.",
      "Always keep the machine in the on position."
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Nothing should be hung on the fire extinguishers, and the area around them should be kept clear so that they may be reached without delay if fire breaks out.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "The following are causes of accidents in the shop:",
    options: [
      "Rushing or hurrying",
      "Overconfidence",
      "Fatigue",
      "Ignorance",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: '"A clean shop is a _______ shop."',
    options: ["safe", "dirty", "fun", "busy"],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Wearing gloves when operating machinery is:",
    options: [
      "Considered a safe practice on a cold day.",
      "Safe, if the gloves are not made of leather.",
      "Permissible if the machine is dirty.",
      "Not a safe practice because the gloves may get caught in moving parts and pull your hand into the machine."
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "When sweeping scraps from a machine or workbench:",
    options: [
      "Use your hand.",
      "Use a piece of wood or a brush since there may be sharp or jagged particles among the scraps.",
      "Use compressed air.",
      "Leave the scraps to show how hard you are working."
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "Compressed air may be used to clean sawdust off the ground under the following circumstances:",
    options: ["Never.", "On Mondays and Wednesdays only.", "If no one is looking.", "If you're wearing pants."],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "When the clean up bell rings the order of procedures should be…",
    options: [
      "Put away project and materials, go to sector, dust, sweep.",
      "Go to sector, Sweep, dust.",
      "Get backpack and wait at door.",
      "Sweep, dust, go to sector, wait."
    ],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "Always keep tools and equipment in:",
    options: [
      "A clean and organized condition.",
      "Wherever you last used them.",
      "Just as you found them.",
      "It doesn't matter as the next class will take care of it."
    ],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "Always check the area you plan to work in to:",
    options: [
      "See that no-one else is going to work there.",
      "See that it is clean, organized, and safe to work in.",
      "Unorganized but can push a few things around to make room for you.",
      "Has good lighting and A/C"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "Never weld, grind, or cut near:",
    options: ["The instructor", "Flammable substances", "Fellow students", "All of the Above"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "Eye protection cannot be worn over prescription glasses.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "What safety precautions does one need to keep in mind when using the plasma table?",
    options: [
      "Smashed fingers and toes, abrasions and cuts",
      "Electric shock",
      "Arc burn, Burns to the skin or eyes",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "Carry long objects:",
    options: [
      "Like a spear.",
      "With the back end high.",
      "With the front end high.",
      "With one hand."
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "_____ need to be worn at all times when in the shop.",
    options: ["Safety glasses", "Gloves", "Hard hats", "Aprons"],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "Only safety glasses need to be worn when grinding, chipping, cutting, or shaping metal with power tools.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "Rags wet with oils or solvents must always be:",
    options: [
      "Folded neatly and placed on a shelf.",
      "Discarded in a covered metal container.",
      "Wadded up and thrown in the trash.",
      "Left on a workbench."
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "When removing scraps of wood from near a moving blade…",
    options: [
      "Grab them fast to avoid the blade.",
      "Remove the guards to get better access to the scrap wood.",
      "Turn the machine off and grab the piece before the blade stops.",
      "Use a long stick or other waste material to push it a safe distance away."
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "Sharp edge tools are:",
    options: ["More dangerous than dull edge tools.", "Safer to use than dull edge tools.", "Scary."],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "When lifting a heavy object you should:",
    options: [
      "Get help.",
      "Keep your back straight and lift with your legs.",
      "Use a lever, dolly, jack, forklift, wheels, or rollers.",
      "Do one or more of the above, depending on the situation."
    ],
    answer: 3
  }
];
